{
	"id" : "113",
	"global_id" : "mt1_l1",
	"instructions" : "Answer the given addition with regrouping. The player will shoot the correct archery target that has the correct answer. Use the mouse control to aim the target and to fire out the arrow.",
	"level 1" : [
		  {
			"Item": 1,
			"Question": "11,+ 9",
			"Correct": 20,
			"Wrong 1": 18,
			"Wrong 2": 21,
			"Wrong 3": 19
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 2,
			"Question": "15,+ 7",
			"Correct": 22,
			"Wrong 1": 23,
			"Wrong 2": 24,
			"Wrong 3": 21
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 3,
			"Question": "17,+ 6",
			"Correct": 23,
			"Wrong 1": 21,
			"Wrong 2": 22,
			"Wrong 3": 24
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 4,
			"Question": "16,+ 7",
			"Correct": 23,
			"Wrong 1": 22,
			"Wrong 2": 24,
			"Wrong 3": 21
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 5,
			"Question": "14,+ 7",
			"Correct": 21,
			"Wrong 1": 19,
			"Wrong 2": 20,
			"Wrong 3": 18
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 6,
			"Question": "15,+ 6",
			"Correct": 21,
			"Wrong 1": 19,
			"Wrong 2": 20,
			"Wrong 3": 22
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 7,
			"Question": "13,+ 9",
			"Correct": 22,
			"Wrong 1": 22,
			"Wrong 2": 19,
			"Wrong 3": 22
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 8,
			"Question": "12,+ 9",
			"Correct": 21,
			"Wrong 1": 20,
			"Wrong 2": 19,
			"Wrong 3": 22
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 9,
			"Question": "11,+ 9",
			"Correct": 20,
			"Wrong 1": 21,
			"Wrong 2": 18,
			"Wrong 3": 19
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 10,
			"Question": "15,+ 5",
			"Correct": 20,
			"Wrong 1": 19,
			"Wrong 2": 21,
			"Wrong 3": 18
		  }
		],
	"level 2" : [
		  {
			"Item": 1,
			"Question": "14,+ 16",
			"Correct": 30,
			"Wrong 1": 28,
			"Wrong 2": 31,
			"Wrong 3": 29
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 2,
			"Question": "12,+ 9",
			"Correct": 21,
			"Wrong 1": 18,
			"Wrong 2": 20,
			"Wrong 3": 19
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 3,
			"Question": "15,+ 16",
			"Correct": 31,
			"Wrong 1": 29,
			"Wrong 2": 30,
			"Wrong 3": 28
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 4,
			"Question": "11,+ 19",
			"Correct": 30,
			"Wrong 1": 28,
			"Wrong 2": 31,
			"Wrong 3": 29
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 5,
			"Question": "16,+ 8",
			"Correct": 24,
			"Wrong 1": 21,
			"Wrong 2": 23,
			"Wrong 3": 22
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 6,
			"Question": "17,+ 6",
			"Correct": 23,
			"Wrong 1": 22,
			"Wrong 2": 24,
			"Wrong 3": 21
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 7,
			"Question": "13,+ 19",
			"Correct": 32,
			"Wrong 1": 30,
			"Wrong 2": 29,
			"Wrong 3": 31
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 8,
			"Question": "15,+ 18",
			"Correct": 33,
			"Wrong 1": 30,
			"Wrong 2": 31,
			"Wrong 3": 32
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 9,
			"Question": "17,+ 14",
			"Correct": 31,
			"Wrong 1": 33,
			"Wrong 2": 30,
			"Wrong 3": 32
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 10,
			"Question": "18,+ 13",
			"Correct": 31,
			"Wrong 1": 32,
			"Wrong 2": 33,
			"Wrong 3": 30
		  }
		],
	"level 3" : [
		  {
			"Item": 1,
			"Question": "17,+ 18",
			"Correct": 35,
			"Wrong 1": 33,
			"Wrong 2": 32,
			"Wrong 3": 34
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 2,
			"Question": "17,+ 16",
			"Correct": 33,
			"Wrong 1": 32,
			"Wrong 2": 35,
			"Wrong 3": 34
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 3,
			"Question": "18,+ 16",
			"Correct": 34,
			"Wrong 1": 33,
			"Wrong 2": 31,
			"Wrong 3": 32
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 4,
			"Question": "16,+ 19",
			"Correct": 35,
			"Wrong 1": 32,
			"Wrong 2": 34,
			"Wrong 3": 33
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 5,
			"Question": "19,+ 14",
			"Correct": 33,
			"Wrong 1": 31,
			"Wrong 2": 30,
			"Wrong 3": 32
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 6,
			"Question": "17,+ 17",
			"Correct": 34,
			"Wrong 1": 32,
			"Wrong 2": 33,
			"Wrong 3": 31
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 7,
			"Question": "12,+ 18",
			"Correct": 30,
			"Wrong 1": 28,
			"Wrong 2": 31,
			"Wrong 3": 29
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 8,
			"Question": "19,+ 15",
			"Correct": 34,
			"Wrong 1": 31,
			"Wrong 2": 33,
			"Wrong 3": 32
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 9,
			"Question": "13,+ 19",
			"Correct": 32,
			"Wrong 1": 29,
			"Wrong 2": 31,
			"Wrong 3": 30
		  },
		  {
			"Item": 10,
			"Question": "15,+ 17",
			"Correct": 32,
			"Wrong 1": 30,
			"Wrong 2": 29,
			"Wrong 3": 31
		  }
		]
}
